Good morning to everyone at midnight.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
We are going to Korea today.
I was worried that we would be alone.
But it looks like we'll get out of Japan safely.
Thank goodness.
We got in pretty early.
So we have a long wait time.
I'm going to take it easy and wait for the plane to Inchon
I'm going to wait for my flight to Inchon, Korea.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye bye!
Bye bye bye!
We have arrived in Korea!
Arrived in Korea
First visit to Korea
I arrived in Korea for the first time!
Now I'm going to eat janggne in Inchon!
Here is janggne
Octopus stew
I'm looking forward to it!
I got this from a cab.
Cab gave this to me!
Safe driving!
He said drive safe!
I've got it right here.
There's no octopus in it.
It's in here, too.
Trigger.
for cleaners
previous
an
searcher
Eat Octopus OK?
I'll eat.
Buda is still left
I'll eat
Puri Puri Pre-prepared.
I'm starving.
Is it bad?
It's a very strange feeling.
I know!
It's warm and raw.
Yes, it is!
Isn't the surface really soft and fluffy?
Yeah, it's really good.
It's really good.
But it's red, and it's not spicy at all.
Really? It's not spicy at all.
You got it.
Yeah, I got it.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Is it good? I'm really enjoying this.
Did you eat the pork? Pork is amazing.
It's really good. The yams are good too.
It's really good. The garlic is really good.
It's so good.
I love kun chi. I love the taste of kun chi.
I can seriously afford it.
Delicious
Taste
I'm finished with the hot pot here.
Yay!
Oh gal
I'm going to go now.
I just came from Inchon Airport by cab.
I'm walking.
I won't fall down.
I've been taking a cab for a long time. If you've been using cabs all your life.
When I reached the limit of my money.
Once you get to Inchon
Inchon and then take a train to
hotel in Dongdaemun
and walk to the hotel.
There are very few people in Incheon.
So few people.
Why?
Bye bye!
That was really good.
It was so good!
We're at the hotel.
You just got here.
From the airport on Sunday.
It took about an hour and a half to get here.
I came to Dongdaemun.
I caught a cab from Dongdaemun.
and went to Dongdaemun after this
to exchange money
I went to Dongdaemun to exchange money
I'm already broke.
I only have 200 yen each.
I'm going to change some money
I'm going to buy some clothes.
Good night.
Okay, let's go! Bye bye!
I'm walking the streets of Dongdaemun.
It's a little bit darker on this side of the street than I expected.
Yes, it is.
It feels like prosperity now.
No, it doesn't.
Isn't it a little cold? Yeah.
It was raining, and I went to the hotel to get an umbrella.
I went back to the hotel to get an umbrella, and I put it out again, and it stopped.
I see.
I'll let you know when I find a good restaurant. Then I'll turn it around again when I find a good restaurant!
Here are two right away.
That's 600 yen.
Wow, it was really delicious!
Bon appétit!
Delicious?
Two right away.
How do you like it?
Mmmm...
Very tasty.
Not spicy at all.
Is it hearty? Yes, it is.
Jaja-jaja-jaja! What is this place?
Anchan, this is a famous market, but it's the same one.
Not here, Mr. Sacchi.
I ate with a bunch of assholes, and I wanted to go to this place, so I did.
What's this? Liver?
Sashimi.
Here comes the sashimi.
Looks good. It's about 1,700 yen.
This is yukke.
You like yukke?
I love it!
I think it's absolutely delicious!
I like it so much lately that I order a lot of it!
That's why I'm so happy to be able to eat so much!
There's definitely a lot of it!
Sumonita
PARK
Is it good?
I've never seen it before.
What kind of fish?
It's not just a crispy fish.
It's got a nice flavor.
Liver.
It's good. Yum!
I'll eat slowly!
I'll eat slowly tomorrow.
I'll eat slowly tomorrow, and when I feel full.
Next time, I'm going to eat hotchpotch!
I'm here for hotchpotch!
Dessert is a special treat!
Delicious-looking hot dishes
They are getting baked!
Looks so good!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Beyotte and
Vitamins
Mulu
Bang, bang, bang, bang!
Hm?
Vitamin
Sweet.
Tastes like aluminum thai, vitamins, and alinamin.
It's delicious.
What do you think?
I just want to eat the biatta.
I want to eat it!
Yuna's dream!
It's your first time in Korea, right?
That's right.
Okay, Soo-chan!
Okay...
Turn that off too!
It stopped!
Yuck!
No, glance, what? This is bad.
I can see why everyone says this is delicious!
Bear!
tan
Search
ences ences
Good night.
The neighbor was messing around next door, so the neighbor must have coco'd it.
I see.
It would have been interesting to see how fast you could switch between the two now.
It should definitely be Cocoa Two.
Let's do our best to live up to it.
Happy, happy, happy.
Did you eat?
I did.
Okay, then.
Dan to Kalmogosm!
Bye-bye.
Good night.